<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="faq_uses">What can I use PawfectPlanner for?</string>
    <string name="faq_uses_text">
        PawfectPlanner helps you:
        • Create detailed, shareable pet profiles.
        • Manage all pet-related tasks: vaccinations, checkups, and custom reminders.
        • Get reminders via notifications or sync with your calendar.
        • Use PawfectGPT to ask anything pet-related – even using your pet’s data if you want!
    </string>

    <string name="faq_missing_breed">Why isn’t my pet’s breed available?</string>
    <string name="faq_missing_breed_text">
        The app uses public pet databases. Currently, it supports known pure-bred cats and dogs.
        If your pet is a mix or a different type (like a parrot or hamster), choose "Other" and enter the type manually.
        Some features like breed-specific weight or lifespan may not work with unsupported pets.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_api_key">Why do I need an API key?</string>
    <string name="faq_api_key_text">
        This is a free app, and we are not allowed to share commercial API keys.
        API keys are required to enable full features like chatbot, breed data, and insights.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_api_get">Where do I get an API key?</string>
    <string name="faq_api_get_text">
        • Dog &amp; Cat Breeds: https://thedogapi.com / https://thecatapi.com
        • Gemini AI: https://makersuite.google.com/app/apikey
    </string>

    <string name="faq_english_only">Why are pet breeds only in English?</string>
    <string name="faq_english_only_text">
        Breed data comes from international sources that are available only in English.
        For now, translations aren’t supported, but you can type your own description.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_offline">Can I use the app offline?</string>
    <string name="faq_offline_text">
        Pet profile creation and breed-based insights require an internet connection.
        Offline mode supports basic manual entry. All data can be updated once you’re online.
        Note: PawfectGPT needs a stable connection to work.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_backup">Can I back up or share my pet’s data?</string>
    <string name="faq_backup_text">
        Currently, data is saved only on your device.
        You can export and share data manually (PDF or text). A cloud backup may be added in the future.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_privacy">Is my data private?</string>
    <string name="faq_privacy_text">
        Your data stays on your device and is never sent to us.
        However, when using APIs (like for breed info or chatbot), your API key may be shared with external providers.
        These services may associate your data with your API key email.
    </string>
</resources>